Pratishtha Bhardwaj

New Delhi, Delhi pratishthabhardwaj7_ew9@indeedemail.com 9711885300

My goal is to become associated with a company where I can utilize my skills obtained from classroom and out of the classroom experience and gain further experience while enhancing the organization productivity and reputation.

Work Experience

Executive

Grey cell PR - Delhi, Delhi January 2020 to Present

Brand Executive

Apex Heights PVT LTD - Delhi, Delhi May 2019 to January 2020

Internship

Weber Shandwick - Gurgaon, Haryana June 2018 to July 2018

Internship

Accessible India Campaign - New Delhi, Delhi June 2016 to July 2016

Govt. of India) as a Social Media Intern.(15th June, 2016 - 25th July, 2016).

• Internship with Sakshi Darshan (Monthly Magazine).

EVENTS CO-ORDINATED

- Volunteer in Accessible India campaign in Ride 4 Accessiblity event at India Gate on 24 July 2016.
- Delegate in Felicitation Programme For Winners of Rio Para Abilympics, T-20 Asia Cup Indian Blind Cricket Team and Indian Blind & Para Judo Team event at Vigyan Bhawan, New Delhi on 28 October 2016.
- Delegate in " MANTHAN" event at Vigyan Bhawan, New Delhi on 16 December 2016.
- Conducted Major events on behalf of Mass Communication Department of KRCHE College as Team Head for 3 consecutive years.
- Conducted National Seminar on "25 Years of Economic Reforms: Issues, Challenges & Solutions" event at KRCHE, GGSIPU, Delhi on 7 & 8 January 2017.
- Organize an event LIHAAZ at Amity University Noida.

Education

Master of Arts in Journalism & Mass Communication

Amity University - Noida, Uttar Pradesh 2017 to 2019

Bachelors of Journalism & Mass Communication in Higher Education

Kasturi Ram College - Delhi, Delhi 2014 to 2017

CBSE

Senior Secondary - Delhi, Delhi 2014

CBSE

School Rohini - Delhi, Delhi 2012

Skills / IT Skills

- DIGITAL MARKETING
- MARKETING
- PAGEMAKER
- PREMIERE
- MS OFFICE

Additional Information

TECHNICAL PROFICIENCY

- ♦ Software MS Office, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Pagemaker, Adobe Premiere Pro, Audacity Sound Editor, Sony Vegas Pro and AVS Video Editor, Coral Draw, QuarkXPress
- Completed one day training on digital marketing from MSME.
- Completed certified training of "The Fundamental of Digital Marketing" by Google in Aug 2019.
- ❖ Participated in 3 day national workshop on "understanding the code of Professional Ethics in a workplace".

ACADEMIC PROJECTS HANDLED

PUBLIC RELATION TRACKING

Brief on the methodology adopted and problem statement

MARKET AND CONSUMER BEHAVIOUR ANALYSIS OF

KAMLA NAGAR, NEW DELHI

Brief on the methodology adopted and problem statement MADE AN INFOGRAPICS ON ADOBE PREMIERE PRO On Different social issues topics DISSERTATION

On Conflict And Challenges Faced By Women Journalists In Electronic Media